bestwebext.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy - Best Downloader Extension

Privacy Policy  
As bestwebext.com , we respect your personal privacy rights and make an effort to ensure this during your time on our site. The explanations regarding the security of your personal information are described below and provided for your information.  
Registration Files  
As with many standard web servers, logistic log files are stored for technical purposes. These files; Your IP address includes standard information such as your internet service provider, browser features, operating system, and login and output pages. Log files are not used for statistical purposes and do not violate your privacy. Your address and other information is not associated with your personal information.

1 Ads  
2 Cookies  
3 External Links  
4 Contact  
Advertisements

We publish ads from outside companies on our site (Google, etc.). These ads may contain cookies and cookies may be collected by these companies and we cannot access this information. We have Google Adsense, etc. Please read the confidentiality agreements from their respective pages.

Cookies

The word ır Cookie – Cookie – is used to describe a small text file that the web page server places on your computer’s hard disk. Some parts of our site may be using cookies to provide user convenience. In addition, through the ads available on the site, cookie and web beacon may be used to collect advertising data. This is entirely possible with your permission, you can change the settings of your browser in accordance with your request is possible.

External Links

The site is linked to different internet addresses. bestwebext.com is not responsible for the contents or confidentiality principles of the sites it provides links to, banner advertisements. The linking process referred to herein is considered to be legally “referenced”

Contact

on the privacy policy applied on the site all kinds of questions, opinions and thoughts you can send us info@www.bestwebext.com.
